-谢谢你陪我妹妹  -不客气
- Thanks for ‭keeping sis company. - My pleasure.
你需要喝一杯
You need a drink.
来给你叫一杯
Let's get you a drink.
你是干什么的  戴尔
So, what do you do, Dale?
我是一名工程师
I'm an engineer.
就像凯西·琼斯那样的吗  戴帽子
What, like Casey Jones, with the hat and...
美国铁路工人  被誉为"勇敢的工程师"
不  傻蛋
No, idiot!
他是那种工程师  不是那种
An engineer engineer, not an "engineer."
戴尔是建东西的
Dale builds things.
我设计东西  主要是溢洪道和排水区域
I design things -- spillways and drainage fields, mostly.
其实都不是我造的
I don't -- I don't actually build them.
很厉害啊
Well, that's cool, yeah.
但你还是能戴帽子的吧
But you could still wear the hat, though, right?
没有什么能阻止你吧
I mean, nothin stoppin' ya.
是啊  应该可以
Oh, yeah, I guess I could.
据我所知  没有规定禁止你戴吧
I'm just saying, there's no rule about that, as far as I know.
你真是讨厌  怎么心情这么好
Hey, you're such a brat. Why the good mood?